Pull request是用户请求对主站点进行更改的方式。
pull request is how users ask for changes to be made on the main site.
现在 当你想对你的项目做一些小的改变时 你可以直接在Github上做这些
Now you can do them directly on Github when you want to make some minor changes to your project.
我们来看看这是怎么做的
So let's take a look at how that's done.
这是我们的项目
So here's our project,
然后进入docs文件夹，看看index。html文件。
and I'm going to go into the docs folder and then take a look at my index.HTML file.
我想做的是改变这个网页的标题，
And what I want to do is maybe change the title of this web page,
因为它实际上是我从另一个项目中复制的东西，
because it's really something I copied from another project,
它叫做布局。
and it's called Layout.
也许在第一页 我要把这个名字改一下
So maybe on this 1st page, I'm going to change this name right here.
要做到这一点，我可以点击这个编辑按钮，
So to do that, I can just hit this edit button right now,
这将带我进入一个非常简单的编辑器。
and that will bring me into a very simple editor.
注意 所有语法都是高亮显示的
Notice that it's all syntax highlighted.
它有行号 这实际上是一个很酷的编辑器
It's got line numbers. It's actually a pretty cool editor.
所以我要把这个布局标题改成学习Git和GitHub，这是这个项目的标题。
And so I'm going to change this layout title to Learning Git and GitHub, which is a title for this project.
然后你可以点击预览预览它的变化
And then you can hit preview to preview that changes.
这将在一个漂亮的小界面中显示您所修改的内容
This will show you what you have modified in a nice little interface.
然后我们可以提交这些更改 就像我们在本地网站上做的那样
And then we can commit these changes just like we would on our local website.
我在这里加一个注释
And I'll add here a note.
你也可以添加一点扩展描述
And you can also add a little bit of an extended description.
它是可选的 所以我将留空
It's optional, so I'm going to leave it blank.
这里可以决定我是从哪封邮件开始的
Here can decide which email I'm doing this from.
这里你也可以选择，就像在本地版本中一样，
And here you can also choose, just like you can in the local version of this,
要提交到主分支或创建一个新分支，
to commit to the main branch or create a new branch,
这将生成所谓的拉取请求。
and this will generate what's called a pull request.
现在我可以给这个分支命名，标题，更改，
Now here I can give this branch name, title, change,
我不会提出改变，对吧?
and I'm going to hate propose changes, right?
现在它所做的是打开所谓的拉取请求。
So now what it's doing is opening up what's called the pull request.
这就是，如果你是别人，或者即使是你自己，
This is how, if you were somebody else, or even if it's yourself,
你可以打开一个请求，根据我们现有的两个不同的分支对这个网站进行修改，
you can open up a request to make changes to this website based on the two different branches that we have,
原来的分支和我刚刚创建的分支。
the original branch and the one I just created.
你不需要做太多
And you don't really need to do much here.
你所能做的就是点击changetitle并创建这个pullrequest
All you can do is either hit change title and create this pull request.
我们点击它
Let's go ahead and hit that.
现在创建一个请求。所以要创造一个改变似乎还有很长的路要走，
Now creates a request. So it just seems like a long way to go to just create a change,
但它在这里做的是创建这个拉取请求，并给它一个数字，
but what it's doing here is creating this pull request, and it's given it a number,
因为你可以有很多这样的东西，然后它就定义了一个关于项目的对话。
because you can have many of these, and then it sort of defined a conversation about the project.
现在这个可以保持开放 你可以做笔记问别人
Now this can remain open, and you can sort of make notes to ask people.
在这里输入一个注释 嘿 你觉得这个怎么样
Type in a note here, hey, what do you think of this?
如果我跟其他人谈论这个头衔的改变，
If I was talking to other people of this title change,
继续点击常见评论，让人们评论你在这里做的事情。
and just continue to hit common common comment and allow people to comment on what you're trying to do here.
然后其他人可以进来
And then other people can come in here
并就是否应该改变这一点发表意见。
and make their comments about whether or not this should be changed.
一旦你完成了这些，你想要合并pull请求，
Once you are done with this, though, you want to merge the pull request,
我们需要做的就是点击合并拉取请求。
And so all we need to do here is click on this merge pull request.
现在我还需要做一件事 就是确认合并 对吧
And now I need to do one more thing, which is confirm the merge, right?
点击确认合并，
So I'm going to click on confirm the merge,
即现在成功合并了请求并关闭了此pull请求。
and that is now successfully merged the request and closed this pull requests.
这是一个漫长的过程 但这就是你起床后的做法
So that's a long process, but it's how you do things on get up.
注意在右边有各种各样的项目管理的东西你可以做
Notice that there's all kinds of project management things on the right hand side that you can do.
除此之外 您还可以添加暹罗
In addition to this, you can add a Siamese.
现在，团队里只有一个人，
Right now, there's only one person in the team,
但如果你有额外的人，
but if you had additional people,
然后你可以指派一个人来审查提出的变更。
then you could assign somebody to review the change that is being proposed.
您还可以添加标签。这是典型的标签，
You can also add labels. So there's the typical label,
所以你可以添加，也许是提议的拉取请求，
so you can add to, perhaps a proposed pull request,
所以你可以在一个特定的话题上寻求帮助。
so you can ask for help on a specific topic.
这看起来不太亮 并把这些标签
This doesn't seem bright, and put any of these labels.
这些都很有用，
Those are kind of useful,
因为你可以根据这些不同的标签来查找或排序。
because you can then look for or sort by these different labels.
您还可以创建里程碑。
You can also create milestones.
里程碑是一种让您定义希望通过代码达到的目标的方法。
Milestones are a way of letting you define targets that you want to reach with your code.
你做的另一个产品管理的事情就是得到Hub
So another product management thing that you do and get Hub.
然后你也可以将拉取请求与问题对齐
And then also you can align the pull request with an issue.
我之前确实给你们看过问题
So I did show you issues before.
你可以创建一个问题 说 嘿 我们需要修改这个项目的标题
You can create an issue and say, hey, we need to fix the title for this project.